http://www.clker.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.
Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Registration Information.
You will provide us information about yourself, your email address when you register to be able to use personalized services.
Email Information.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.
Web Site Use Information
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called web beacons or clear gifs to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.
The website usage information is collected both by us, and by third party tools that we use like google analytics, which are used to serve the same purpose.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services on our website. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site and new services. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by opting out of any email correspondence using the links provided in the email message. We neither share your personal information nor sell to any other parties, unless required to do so under legal proceedings.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
As you browse our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other visitors. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us and the third part tools we use to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.
Google is a third party vendor that provides advertisements on clker.com. Google uses a technology called DART cookies that help them serve ads based on the type of websites you visit including clker.com and other websites on the internet. You may opt out of this type of technology by visiting this page: Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
We NEVER enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties that will lead to selling your email or information. Plain and simple - your information won't be sold.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and other facts that we think you will find valuable. You will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by using links at the bottom of the email.
Advertise on clker
Report a bug
Request a feature
tag
FAQ
Terms of Use & Disclaimer
Privacy
DMCA notices
Clker.com is owned by Rolera LLC, 2270 Route 30, Oswego, IL 60543 support\at\clker\dot\com
